Why did I say something so awful?
為什麼說了那麼過分的話呢？
Do you…
香坂
even have fun when you're with me?
跟像我這樣的人在一起開心嗎？
Huh?
什麼？
Don't you think someone else would be better?
如果不是我會更好嗎？
First of all, congratulations on winning the Tsume Shogi Championship.
首先，恭喜你在 之前的詰將棋冠軍賽中取得優勝
Thank you.
謝謝
I haven't changed at all since then.
我和那時相比，一點改變都沒有
I don't understand Kagiya's feelings.
我不明白鍵谷的感覺
Just when I thought we were getting closer…
好不容易覺得更親近一點
Ah, so it's finally heading towards divorce.
唉，還是離婚了啊
She was involved in an affair not too long ago, right?
她之前才傳出婚外情，對吧？
I saw that on the internet news too.
我也有看到網路新聞
It's kind of sad, isn't it?
感覺真難過呢
To think they swore love to each other, only to end up divorcing.
好不容易發誓彼此相愛 結果卻離婚了
Well, I think that's also a viable option.
我想那也是種選擇吧
Huh?
咦？
You know how you only realize something after you've lost it?
不是有那種失去後才明白之類的嗎？
If they were truly important to each other they can always get back together.
如果真的重視彼此 就會再重修舊好的吧？
I'm in favor of divorce too.
我也贊成離婚
You too?
你也是？
Yes.
對
If they talk about it, and still think it won't work,
如果談過後還是行不通
maybe it's worth trying to let go.
那就值得試試看不是嗎？
Always trying to make things work. It's impossible.
什麼事都要全力以赴，也太辛苦了
After all, swearing love to each other is just for show.
再說，發誓彼此相愛只是做做樣子吧
For show…
做做樣子…
You can't tell from appearances whether or not
有沒有好好正視自己
they really see each other for who they are.
單從表面是看不出來的吧？
Seriously facing someone isn't just about pretty words.
認真面對一個人 不是只有說說漂亮話而已
It's about accepting that there will be scars.
這代表可能會受一些傷呢
Did I truly face Kagiya?
我有認真面對鍵谷嗎？
I may not understand Kagiya's feelings but I also didn't properly convey my own.
雖然我不明白鍵谷的感覺 但我也沒有好好表達自己的感覺
I'll never get closer to him this way.
這樣是沒辦法再更接近鍵谷的吧？
EIKOU MAINTENANCE
（榮光維修公司）
Kosaka…
香坂
Can we talk for a moment?
可以聊一下嗎？
I'm sorry for showing up at your workplace like this.
不好意思，突然跑到你工作的地方
It's okay.
不會
I never know how to handle personal space.
我總是很不會拿捏距離感
I was scared people will dislike me,
我很怕會被討厭
so I decided to not get too involved with others.
所以不太會和別人深交
But…
但是…
I want you to know how I feel,
我想讓你知道我的感覺
and I want to understand your feelings better.
我也想要更瞭解你的感受
Please tell me how you feel.
請告訴我你的感覺
Do you hate me?
你已經討厭我了嗎？
I got the order wrong.
順序搞錯了
Huh?
什麼？
I should've started out by telling you.
我應該先告訴你的
I…
我…
Decided not to see you until I became a full-time employee.
擅自下了決定 在當上正職前不再跟你見面
Full-time employee?
正職？
Yes.
對
At my workplace
在我們公司
you can't become a full-time employee without a driver's license,
如果沒有駕照 是沒辦法成為正職人員的
so I'm currently attending driving school.
所以我正在上駕訓班
For the past three years,
我在這三年來
I kept thinking I was fine with nothing.
都覺得自己一無所有也沒關係
Since my dream didn't come true…
因為沒有實現夢想
I thought the only thing that's left was just to survive.
就覺得人生只要活下去就好
But…
但是
After meeting you,
遇見你之後
for the first time, I felt a desire.
我第一次感受到了欲望
Desire?
欲望？
I want to become a person you wouldn't be embarrassed to be with.
我想成為和你在一起 也不會讓你感到丟臉的人
I want to change.
我想要改變
I'm really sorry about the other day.
之前真的很抱歉
I was worried that I might not be worthy of you,
我很擔心自己是否配不上你
and it made me anxious.
覺得非常不安
Kosaka.
香坂
Yes?
是
I…
我…
love you.
喜歡你
So…
所以
I mean…
那個…
It would be nice if…
如果你願意…
You would…
和我交往的話
Be my girlfriend.
我會很高興
I also…
我也…
I love you too.
我也喜歡你
It's the first time in my adult life that I've liked someone this much.
這是我長大成人之後 第一次這麼喜歡一個人
I want to be spend more time with you tonight.
我想多和你在一起
Me too…
我也是
I'll make some tea.
我去泡茶
Okay.
好
Or would you prefer something stronger?
還是你想喝點酒呢？
It's like we're magnets drawn together this strongly.
就像磁鐵會彼此強烈吸引一樣
I'm actually going to do it.
真的要做了
With Kagiya…
我和鍵谷
May I undress you?
我能脫嗎？
Yes.
好
Is this okay too?
這個也可以嗎？
Can I turn off the light?
可以關燈嗎？
Ah… Yes.
啊，好
I'm sure he must have experience.
鍵谷一定是有經驗吧
Ouch.
好痛
I'm sorry, it hurts a little bit, I think.
對不起，我覺得好像有點痛
I'm sorry.
抱歉
It's fine.
不會
It's…
我…
My first time.
是第一次
What?
什麼？
She's taken aback, isn't she?
她果然很驚訝吧
If I do something weird, please tell me.
如果我做了奇怪的事，請告訴我
No… It's my first time too.
不，我也是
What?
咦？
It's also my first time.
我也是第一次
Really?
真的嗎？
Yes.
對
I've always been embarrassed about it, but if it's the same for you,
這讓我一直覺得很丟臉 但如果你也一樣
maybe it's a good thing.
也許是件好事
I agree.
我也覺得
Um…
那個…
Can I touch you here?
我可以摸這裡嗎？
Yes.
好
Um… be gentle.
請溫柔一點
Give me a minute.
請等我一下
Okay.
好
I…
我…
don't know if I can do it.
能做得順利嗎？
I put it on.
我戴好了
Okay.
好的
Could you…
你可以…
Spread your legs a bit more?
再把腳打開一點嗎？
Yes.
知道了
Does it hurt?
會痛嗎？
It doesn't.
不會痛
It's fine.
沒問題
But…
但是…
Please don't stop.
請不要停下來
I'm sorry.
對不起
Huh?
咦？
I…
我…
I don't think I can do it.
我可能沒辦法做
I'm sorry too.
我才是該對不起
Maybe we should just stop for now.
也許今天就算了吧？
Yes… That might be best.
嗯…說的也是
He must have felt uncomfortable.
鍵谷一定很不愉快吧
Did I disappoint her?
香坂一定很失望吧
Even though it feels good, why does it hurt there?
明明身體很舒服 為什麼只有這裡很痛呢？
I always mess up when it really matters.
我果然都會在關鍵時刻搞砸
When he said he liked me, it made me so happy.
他說喜歡我時，明明覺得很開心的
She said she liked me, and wanted to do it with me…
她說了喜歡我，想要和我做的
I want to do it, but…
明明想和這個人做的
Please don't force yourself.
不要勉強自己
I don't want you to feel pain.
我不想讓你留下很痛的回憶
I'm not forcing anything.
我沒有勉強
Even if it hurts, I want to do it with you.
就算會痛，我也想和你做
Because I love you.
因為我喜歡你
I was always so embarrassed about having no experience.
因為沒有經驗，我一直都覺得自卑
Everyone else seems to be able to do it, so why am I the only one who can't?
大家都能做得理所當然 為什麼只有我做不到呢？
I wanted to be someone who had had sex, and I even thought that anyone would do.
為了想成為有經驗的人 還曾想過對象是誰都可以
But now…
但現在…
Is it all in?
全部進去了
Yeah.
嗯
It's in.
進來了
I'm glad my first time was with him.
第一次是跟鍵谷，真是太好了
I love you.
我喜歡你
Kosaka.
香坂
It's warm.
好溫暖
What I always wanted was…
我一直想要的是…
This.
這種感覺
I'm kind of hungry.
感覺肚子有點餓呢
Come to think of it, we haven't had dinner, have we?
說起來，我們沒吃晚餐吧？
That's true.
對耶
Is it melon?
這是黃瓜嗎？
Yes.
對
A senior at work brought it for us.
公司的前輩幫我買的
It's good.
很好吃
The word for losing one's virginity
失去處女這件事
is written with the characters for "breaking a melon."
似乎會寫成“破瓜”來形容
Breaking a hard melon…
把堅硬的瓜弄破…
I thought it sounded painful and was a bit scared of it.
感覺很痛，讓人覺得有點害怕
But now I understand.
但現在我明白了
Getting close to someone's heart is a painful thing.
要接近某人的心，原來是會痛的
But something more lies beyond the pain.
但在痛之外，一定還有多可能性
Hey! That's dangerous.
喂！很危險啦
Oh, man.
喔，天啊
It's so good already.
一開始就超棒的
-That didn't work out. -So close.
-沒辦法 -就差一點
DRIVER'S LICENSE
（駕照）
-Your turn next, Maiko. -Yes.
-麻衣子，換你了 -好
That's why even though I may be creating scars
我今天或許也會留下傷痕
I still want to keep moving forward.
但我還是想繼續前進